

2150 Blackhawk St Clermont, FL 34714

312-972-0833 24gcima@gmail.com

Profile

Driven retail manager with 26 years experience,

including opening and closing procedures, forklift certification, warehouse functions, and additional responsibilities; which include handling, vendors, FedEx, UPS, and deliveries. Efficient and productive with the ability to lead a team and be a team player. Fluent in both English and Spanish.

Experience

Store Manager, Family Dollar; Chicago, IL – 2017-2019

Planed out sales, worked with vendors, and scheduled the rotation of product stock throughout the store. Prepared biannual payroll and budgets. Hired, trained, supervised, motivated, and developed employees. Coached Sales Associates on product knowledge through in-store product training. Ensured proper cash controls and loss prevention procedures were in place and followed.

Assistant Store Manager, Kmart; Chicago, IL – 1991-2017

Graduate of Kmart Academy. Assistant Store Manager of Corporate Academy Chicago. Managers for various departments including, food service (License from 02/28/2017-02/28/2022), operations, and grocery and a layout planner for the store. Lead to multiple departments, including garden, electronics, bedding, hard home, sports, toys. Stock Room Supervisor. Receiving Supervisor. Replenishment Supervisor. Cash office clerk. 605 Clerk Associate for the linen, display, and showroom departments.

Education

Steinmetz College Preparatory; Chicago, IL – Diploma, 1993